What's up, guys?
Are you enjoying your Saturday?
I mean, Sunday!
Getting high on the... HEMISY?
Oh, yeah.
I know it's early for you guys, for some of you.
Some others, maybe not so much early.
Dramatic entrance?
Yeah, I'm in a good mood today.
I feel like saying silly words.
I feel like moving my mouth in such a way that I produce sound waves, which sounds silly.
I like that.
I love the surprise.
Me too, man.
I wasn't planning on streaming, but then I was like, you know what?
I'm gonna stream.
And right after I thought that, someone on Discord wrote, no noise to stream today?
The chance of that is just amazing.
Like, the coincidence there was perfect.
So I had the perfect opportunity to send a nice GIF as a response.
Insert drip noise?
Oh, here we come.
Ah, that was pretty decent.
I've been better at it in the past.
Interrupting me watching your Minecraft vods with this surprise unscheduled stream.
That's right.
Get off those Minecraft vods and get in here instead.
I like it.
Those sounds produced by your vocal cords and modified by your mouth are indeed amusing.
I mean, what are sounds but complicated air like airflow, right?
That's a quote from Succession.
Lovely show.
He was just randomly browsing Twitch.
Awesome.
Very cool.
I had the Noida itch.
What can I say?
The good old Noida itch.
Strikes again.
Attack Child.
Indeed.
I make references to Succession all the time.
I wonder how many people catch that.
Attack Child is one of the more obvious ones, you know?
But I just love the sentence, what are words but complicated airflow.
It's such a good sentence.
I think I'm paraphrasing a little bit, but that's essentially what the quote was.
Can we get this emote, please?
I'm not sure what emote you're talking about, little Light Knight.
Three stars.
Any big goals for today?
Always big goals.
The goal is to explore and take and go wherever the wind guides us, basically.
I have more and more knowledge after every run, and I feel like all that knowledge will soon help me reach some kind of god status in this game.
You know, maybe I can join the ranks of the gods.
Oh, they posted a link.
Put it in the Discord, Light Knight.
In the channel related channel, funnily enough.
On the Discord, I usually look in there for stuff like that.
You can post a link there and I can see it.
But I would love to put in more emotes.
I have lots of spots.
Right, the service here is weird and slow and fucking my dad.
I already know who says that.
You don't even need to tell me where that quote comes from.
It's from, oh man, I forget his name now, but it's the very rude and short, very weird guy.
I forget his name now, but you know who it is.
Very memorable character for sure.
What's the Discord invitation?
It should be in the panels down below, on the Twitch.
Hopefully it is there, I'm actually not sure.
Wait a minute.
Is it there or not?
I just went on my own Twitch.
Yeah, it should be there.
Hopefully that link works as well.
Sometimes the links don't work.
But yeah, you can join there and post suggestions in there.
Okay, well this was a bit of an impromptu stream here, so let's go.
I'm just gonna have some fun.
Play some more noise, I'm excited.
I'll see you guys on the other side.
Adios, friendos.
I just caught the last message before I close, someone saying have fun.
Thank you.
I will.
I promise.
Okay.
Oh nice, I was just at the beginning of a run.
And oh yeah, that's right, swamp potion.
I played Noita for a long time and all I got was this potion filled with swamp water.
I remember making that joke.
Or was it mud?
Okay.
Subhortas, my buddies.
Rude, one of the big discoveries I made last time was that I can heal in Heezy Base if I have pheromone.
That's actually... that's a huge deal.
Or I guess anywhere where those enemies are.
I need to put them on my side and they will heal me.
As long as I protect them, I guess.
If they die, it's rip.
That's a big deal, guys.
Like that combined with the whole discovering the worm blood stuff and man, I just feel like I'm getting so good at this game.
You know?
With all the knowledge.
Makes me so much more able to have a good run.
Thank you.
Now there's a wand up there.
There's no other way to get there.
I think I need to blow open a hole in that.
How do I do it, though?
The bomb I have right now is not sticky.
Hmm.
If I bomb right here, maybe it's enough.
It's gonna be close.
Beautiful.
I underestimated the radius of that explosion.
A circle of stillness.
I need to get rid of this swamp and get real water.
Although I think swamp may serve the same purpose.
I need to test that on... Oh, pheromone!
Now we're prepared.
In fact, hold on, I just got an idea.
Why don't we just use pheromone on the fire enemies?
Let them become friends and then we just shoot them.
How is that not an amazing idea?
Like it sounds so simple in hindsight when you say it like that, right?
But I feel like it's a fantastic idea.
They're so hard to deal with in the beginning.
Throw some pheromone on them.
Boom bada bing.
And they will now bring lots of happiness and they will kiss you a ring.
All that, you know?
Because they're on our side.
These guys are the worst.
Okay, let's test this.
I have swamp water here.
I guess it works.
Smooth and clean.
Just how I like it.
There's oil here.
That's something I don't like.
In fact, I don't particularly enjoy oil.
I'm an anti-oil man.
Ah, that's a steel beam.
Prevents access there.
Oh, I heard you.
But I was looking up here.
So I was like... because I looked up here and I heard the sound, I was like, wait.
Is he up there?
Then I missed him completely down here.
That was funny.
He really bamboozled me there.
Oh, he kills himself.
Love to see that.
That's all wood.
That's gonna burn.
I can get through there.
Can't get through here, though.
Unless this is gonna fall down here and start burning this, too.
Man, I am a complete oracle.
I predict the future easily.
And this guy's gonna fall down with it.
Oh, he's having a bad day.
Why is he not taking damage?
Okay, there we go.
So I... let me water myself.
Because then... I should be sort of harder to catch fire.
Actually, I kinda wanna... So, protect you.
Okay, we gotta do a quick test here.
We gotta do a quick test.
I am full on water.
Wow!
How did I not know that?
It's completely protecting you.
It's not like, oh, there's a chance.
It is actually completely protecting me.
What the fuck?
How did I never...
I mean, it does say that.
But I thought, oh, you know what?
It's just a little harder to catch fire.
If you stand in the fire, dude.
Oh my god!
I'm actually speechless.
I can't believe I did not realize that until now.
This run is already a success.
No matter what happens now if I die, doesn't matter.
The fact that I discovered that already makes this run a W.
That's incredible.
That is actually incredible.
So, it's like immunity from fire, basically.
Probably not immunity from lava, I don't think.
Because that would dry out your clothes quite quick, right?
I am flabbergasted.
I cannot believe it.
This may be one of the worst things that I've done, or one of the worst things that I've been oblivious to so far in this game.
I mean, I knew there was an effect there, you know, but I just didn't realize it was that effective.
That's wild.
And if I use swamp, that's more than enough.
This is going to change everything, guys.
I wonder if you can do some kind of wet build.
You know, just some way to always have your clothes be wet.
Oh, nice.
Whoop!
I heard you.
Wand!
Wait, what did I find?
Right.
Circle of stillness.
Actually, hold on.
Oh,
it froze it immediately.
I didn't realize... Oh my god, I'm discovering all kinds of things right now.
I should just use this on the fire enemies.
And then go up there and go like, ee!
Give them a swift kick in the nuts.
And a problem they shall pose no more.
In fact, I'm going to... speak it off!
Hey!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Come here.
Hey, bitch!
Circle of stillness is sick!
Dude, it feels like I'm on some next level IQ today.
What's happening here?
What's happening?
Why is everything going so well?
Holy shit!
This is wild!
I have a sentence.
Even without the help of Gorb.
Only some of you are going to get that one.
Take that.
There we go.
We got a portal.
This is going swimmingly.
I am so pleased with myself.
Now, can I go this way here?
Hello!
Oh, ee!
Yeah!
Not today, sir.
I can't get over.
I discovered the water thing.
Like, I knew it was there.
Ah!
I mean, I'm happy, but I'm also sad.
Mostly happy.
I would say 68% happy.
One Sigma happy.
I mean, that's not technically correct, the way I just said that.
But you know what I mean.
Aye, aye, aye, aye.
For some reason, that looked like I did 40 Crit.
Hold on.
Bloody clothes protected from fire, so I guess that also completely negates it.
I need to become bloody.
I need Wertha, Wertha, Wertha.
That's what I need.
Boink!
Mix it up good.
And look at this, it all becomes swamp now, too.
It's not actually becoming water.
Becoming water.
If you make swamp with the toxic sludge, it becomes swamp.
Wait, now I wonder if I put anything in here, it becomes that.
That would be kind of crazy.
Like, let's say I put Ambrosia in there.
Does it become Ambrosia?
We gotta test that.
What's going on here?
That looks mysterious.
Shotgun, dude!
Another one!
Oh, headshot!
My aiming is also out of this world right now.
I am on another level.
Right now.
Ah, look at this!
We gotta do the same technique.
Whoa!
I thought I was dodging in time.
This is a dangerous spot to be... Why there's so many Barneys over there.
Hey, Barney!
I see you there.
There we go.
Come here.
Yeah, come here.
You know you want to come here.
Yes, yes.
Fuck you!
Wait, did I do 69 damage there?
That's almost incredible.
Okay, so watch this.
Can I also... Wait.
Of course it would work like that.
Guys, I've made three major discoveries.
In the span of, what is it?
Ten minutes?
Today is crazy.
Oh!
Black hole and this is a trap.
That's electricity.
The best way to do this would be...
Let's think about this.
I wonder if I can grab that and quickly get out.
Before it actually happens.
Okay, here's what I'm going to do.
I'm going to bomb this.
Drain the water.
And then...
I'm going to try and pay attention when I actually take this.
How long it takes for this thing to activate, just for the future.
I probably should have bombed this side.
No, no, I shouldn't, because then I wouldn't be able to test this thing I'm about to test.
Let me mix it.
Come on, flow down.
Flow, damn it!
Okay, that should be okay.
Let's do it quick, let's do it quick.
We may die here.
Okay, it was almost completely instant.
Scary stuff, scary stuff.
So you actually got to be insanely quick.
Huerta!
How's your...
How many shots do you need, sir?
Is he a special Huerta?
Hold on.
Is he actually?
Oh, yeah!
Look at this.
69 kills as well.
What is it with this number?
Popping up everywhere lately.
So I think that guy does have more HP than the normal Huerta.
They just look extremely similar.
Uh, that's a frog.
Watch this.
Oh my god, I'm a genius.
Swamp it up.
Massive swamp operation.
Polymorphine?
Uh, oh shit!
That guy throws that stuff.
Oh!
Oh, he better die from this.
You can't do something like that and get away with it.
No way.
Is he not dying?
He's oiled up, man.
Oh wait, of course, I have an idea, I have an idea.
Yes!
So good!
Polymorphine?
Nah.
Nobody wants that.
Come here.
Nice.
Okay.
Oil?
Like, okay, so, you know what, actually, okay.
I'm gonna make a promise to myself here.
Or like a, uh, what do you call it?
Something I need to do.
I need to be more willing to experiment with different spells in different settings.
So like, Circle of Stillness, I sort of knew what it did, right?
But I need to try it more.
Like, when I discover a new spell, I need to think logically here.
Because if I didn't think logically, I wouldn't have discovered what I just discovered before, right?
I need to do something like that more often.
Whoa!
Someone has a black hole!
Who are you?
Wait, I...
Jesus, what a shot!
Well done.
Ah, it's you, huh?
Come here.
That's right.
Hand it over, bitch!
Oh, wait, he's my friend.
Where's the wand?
Let the wand go.
Eh?
Wait.
Oh, is it there?
Um, let's see.
0.03, 1.5, this is definitely just the better wand.
Even though they're both shuffled, but yeah, take this.
Here's what I can do, though.
I can use this for a while, empty it, and then take the other one.
How about that?
In fact, I have an idea what to use it for as well.
Oh, my God.
It's kind of hard to aim the...
I guess I have to aim with my mouse there.
I need to think about that.
Like, the kick misses a lot when I do it.
Pheromone.
Like, I have a great idea what to do with these black holes.
Um...
I think I'm gonna...
That's how we do it.
Very sweet.
That guy's not dead.
Circle of Stillness is dope.
Oh, two of those guys that throws bottles.
Another one.
A lot of HP on those.
What are they called?
Bottle-throwing guys.
Tulihisi.
Okay.
I wonder if that means alcoholic.
Hesian alcoholic.
There we go.
That took a while.
It's very hard to aim the kick.
I gotta say.
And you know what?
I feel like I discovered...
volcanic rock.
I feel like I find Circle of Stillness quite often in the hemisphere.
So...
It's nice to know that I can utilize it in such a good manner.
Oh, no.
I should get down here.
What have we got?
Empty.
Dammit.
Anyway, I want to use my black holes for the dark cave.
I have another one with three more black holes on it.
And that is actually the one I want to bring with me, because it's a better one.
Now these guys...
open up that, and we blow up this one too.
Beautiful.
Let's get bloody close.
Protection from fire.
Nice.
So now we're 15% bloody.
We should be able to just do that.
Okay, here we are.
Is that... what is that?
That is either pheromone or...
berserkium.
It's hard to tell.
Whoops.
What's that?
Oh, so maybe this...
What is it?
Fire potion.
Nah, I don't want that.
Do not want it.
Now this guy.
Let me get in here.
Ah!
Hello, we got a firecracker man.
I do wonder how much damage those firecrackers do.
Polymorphine.
Okay, so I want to go down here now and watch this.
Oh, sweet.
Yes!
Beautiful.
Oh, no.
I'm out of water.
I'm gonna do...
Wait, why was that so slow?
Oh, we can get more water here.
Nice!
Fill up the water bottle.
Nothing like fresh water from a creek.
And we grab the other black hole wand now.
Black hole wand.
Where was it?
The enemy was using it somewhere.
It was hard to see because it was lying down on the floor somewhere.
Maybe over here.
This will be hard to find, I think.
Oh, no.
This is not the way.
So, hold on.
I used the black hole here.
And I used that after I found the wand.
So, it should go this way then.
I must have gone this way.
Down here.
Is that it?
No.
That was a bit of gold.
Ah, here we go.
There it is.
Okay, now.
Actually, hold on.
It is draining quite nicely here.
Um...
Question, though.
We need a wand that can briefly see in here.
We don't have anything like that, right?
Last time we had something that could see.
Um...
Okay, let's come back here.
Let's let this drain for a bit.
Maybe we can even find a spell wand in here that will have some kind of light on it.
I mean, we have to explore this place anyway.
So, let's do that.
Let's explore the rest.
Another portal.
And a Hymnus.
Rusted metal.
Wow, this thing is just completely closed off, huh?
It does look like all the portals are always right next to each...
I guess they are.
They're like...
along the bottom part of every level.
I was here.
I can get up there, I think.
Wait a minute.
Oh, no.
The enemy used to...
The enemy used to have all the black holes!
Oh, that's fine.
I was like, I didn't use these.
But the enemy did.
The goddamn fireman.
Okay, I want to get up there and teach these guys a lesson.
What?
Hold on.
I can use this to get in.
Bunch of whiskey in there.
Watch this.
This is how we do it.
Ultimate explosion.
Burn it all!
And grant me access to thine chamber.
Oh, yeah.
We even got to water ourselves here.
There we go.
Maximum immunity to fire.
Oh, it's lovely.
Look at this!
It's completely immune!
Let's be careful here, though.
Water me up.
Completely immune.
This is wild.
No.
58 HP.
Decent.
Worm pheromone.
Sure.
What if I freeze you?
I'm just going to kill you.
Whoa, that was close.
There we go.
What a mess.
I won!
Dude, it's become part of my playstyle now to water myself every time I see fire.
Lava potion.
That seems a bit dangerous.
That's a trap.
Can I get in there?
Not really.
Unless... Okay, let's try something crazy here.
Can I freeze this earth and make it brittle?
No.
Okay.
Worth a try, I think.
This looks suspicious to me.
Do we have to fill that with water?
Uh-huh.
Suspiciousness.
If only I had some black holes.
If only I didn't waste those few shots I had.
Whoa.
Actually, hold on.
I can probably...
If I aim up.
Yes?
This way?
No, wait.
I can't get it up there.
Maybe I can just walk up there.
Never mind.
I think I'm playing really well right now.
Now, this is just wood.
But if I burn this up here...
I want to fill this with water.
I feel like something will happen then.
But I also want to get in...
Oh!
I also want to get in there.
That is just frozen forever, huh?
I don't really have anything to get in, unfortunately.
Need to find some explosives.
There's fire here!
Maybe I can use that.
That's not going to spread over there, I don't think.
Unless this oil comes down and spreads and then...
Nah, I don't think so.
Let's give it a bit of time.
No explosives here.
Oh, there's fire up there!
But no, I need explosives.
Oh, there's one.
I think that's enough.
I feel like it's going to explode at some point.
I'm scared.
Aw, man!
Wait, just get it over here.
Come on.
There!
There we go!
That's what I'm talking about.
Let's blow it up.
Yes!
That is...
I think that is the toxic shit spreading.
That is not a bad wand.
It's a non-shuffle.
This black hole is dead anyway.
Let's see here, this is shuffle.
Maybe just replace my bombs.
Yup.
It's the acid.
Flammable gas.
Now that's taken care of.
What should I do next?
Oh yeah, I wanted to go west again.
Let's go see if it's drained all the way.
Is there something in here?
No.
I have not been up there either.
Oh, wait a minute, I can get in there.
Actually, I can just walk around.
I haven't even been up there.
Wow, hold on.
I'm going to get up there first.
Also, how good is this wand?
Like, okay.
Could be better.
Toxic hammers.
I'm out of water.
Shit, can't get in there.
I'm really starting to value these explosive barrels here.
Or boxes.
Wait, what am I doing with this again?
Oh, never mind.
I am not using it for anything.
Back to the cave.
Hold on a second here.
This does not dig, right?
No, not at all.
Because there is still health to be had at the top of the mountain.
Would be nice to grab that as well before we move on.
But for now, this will do.
Let me just confirm here.
It's empty.
Look at this.
Do I dare?
Oh shit, I'm under water.
Where do I go up?
I'm under water still over here.
Oh no, this is going to be bad, isn't it?
This is a bad idea.
It's just a bad idea.
Damn it all.
Well, I have 700 gold.
I think it's okay to move on.
Let's go.
Let me wait with that health.
Ah, now we find light.
Trick grade, projectile repulsion fields.
Melee immunity is great.
I'm taking it.
Because that means fungal caverns, baby.
Let's go with that one.
Some light.
That one.
Maybe...
I think that's... Actually, maybe that one too.
Maybe this one could be cool.
Thundercloud.
Would that be cool?
I'm not sure.
We need something to dig with.
Do we have anything?
Yeah, we have this one.
Okay.
Let's see then.
What we can make.
What is our best wand?
Probably this one.
0.38.
So this one actually removes a bunch of castellae too, right?
And recharge time.
So let's say we go with...
Hold on, let me test some things first here.
Dum-dum-dum-dum.
Then it alternates.
It shoots that, then it shoots that, which shoots that, then it shoots that, then it shoots that, which shoots that, and so on.
See, it is cool to put this one after because that means you can dig wherever this impacts.
See that?
But it sort of bounces off in a weird way.
That's the only thing.
That's a bit annoying.
What I really need is some wand that...
Or like a double spell.
Or something like that.
It's 0.18.
0.35 recharge.
0.45.
Dammit.
Yeah, I'm not sure.
I do like the idea of having a dig at the end.
You know what I mean.
That's also pretty cool.
But, I mean...
Having some light is not a bad idea.
I'm not sure I like this too much.
That's not bad.
But I think I'm gonna stick with the simple option here.
Just go with some spark bolt.
Dum-dum-dum.
The same.
Let's just go like that.
That's fine with me.
Actually, Wollong, it's better to put it on this.
No, it's not because recharge time.
Recharge is the big one.
But if I do this...
It's faster.
Worse.
How about that?
Nah.
Put it here.
And then we're gonna have a dig at the end.
Yeah, I like this.
Just so we can dig a little bit at the same time.
And then we're gonna have circle of stillness.
Put it on a shitty wand.
Like, I don't know.
What is the shitty wand?
This one, I guess.
Wait, these are almost exactly the same.
What the fuck?
Yo, these two wands are the same.
Like, exact replicas.
What the hell are the chances of that?
Look.
Every single stat.
It's the same.
That's wild.
Okay.
Well, I guess that is it.
No, wait, actually, hold on.
I want this.
It's the small one.
That's actually good.
I like that.
But let's keep this number one and have this number two.
Why not?
Yeah.
That seems good to me.
I should probably heal.
Heal and then we move on.
Could also grab a refresh.
But I don't think it's worth it yet.
The refresh is gonna be the late game thing that will allow me to heal.
You know?
If I find the healing spell, I can always refresh it and get more.
That's a big deal.
I know I said last time I shouldn't be afraid of the gods, but I am.
I don't want to anger them, man.
If I find peace with gods, I take it.
Also, I need to take a piss real quick.
Bear back.
Hey, I'm back.
Dude, I am so hyped to play this game today.
I am... I think I'm gonna play it for a while.
And I may actually order some food at some point, too.
I don't usually do that, but I feel today special for some reason.
I feel it, you know?
Just to keep going even more.
I'm starting to develop a little hunger, which is weird because I ate not so long ago.
What is that thing up there?
Just a grey rock hanging out at the ceiling.
Yo, wait a minute.
This is a solid want.
This luminous drill hits them every time.
I'm doing 13 damage per shot.
Oh, I'm taking damage.
Oh, wait, I can't take damage from these guys either.
Oh, it doesn't dig very well.
It's kind of bad at that, but other than that...
Go here...
Actually, no, no, no.
Do the top part first.
Doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo.
Hey, there's a little room in there.
Oh!
Fuck!
Goddammit.
I'm... fuck!
Oh, I got no more water.
Die!
It's ever... it's... I'm fucked.
This is a... fucking disaster.
Why did I do that?
I wasn't thinking.
I wasn't thinking!
Oh, man, that was dumb!
Oh, well, we lost half HP.
It could be worse.
Although it's hard to imagine how, but, you know...
Let me cope with him, okay?
Goddammit.
Guess I'm not going that way.
Also, does this hit me?
Because I feel like I shot this at the wall like that and see how it bounces off.
Let's double check.
Okay!
I don't take damage from that.
That's actually really solid information.
Good to know.
But it is super good, because it does 13 damage per shot now instead.
Oh, I'm poisoned again.
Water me?
Go.
Oh, that's spraying lava everywhere.
That's...
Also, I'm standing in a bad spot here.
Let's get rid of that, huh?
It died.
Nice.
Is that gold?
Hey!
Solid.
37 crit there.
Got some water, whenever you can.
Much important.
So, this one is not really good at digging, because it shoots in the random direction, right?
So, if I needed digging, I need to put it on a separate thing.
Maybe just on its own, on a wand.
The luminous drill, that is.
Makes it good!
Aha!
Hello!
Oh, hold on, hold on.
Let's play this safe.
This rat is annoying me.
Let's get rid of him.
Another luminous drill!
And a decent wand!
That is better than this wand.
So, is that gonna...
That's digging!
That's digging, baby!
Wait, oh!
That guy has a wand!
I feel like I start to see these guys everywhere now.
I didn't see them in the beginning.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, wow, that hurt a lot.
Oh, no.
Oh, shh!
Oh, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Calm down, calm down.
Let's circle of stillness this guy when he comes.
Is the audio bugging?
Oh, no, oh, no, oh, no, oh, no, oh, no!
Ah!
I'm almost dead!
Is this the end?
I don't wanna go through the portal, man.
I would rather die and start over.
I'm not kidding.
I will not go through that portal.
I am fighting this guy with one HP.
Wish me luck, guys.
This duel is happening.
He doesn't get...
He doesn't get frozen by that at all.
Rip.
Yep.
Yep, yep, yep, yep.
That's fine, though.
That's okay.
Let's update the death here.
That is 71.
Ion Sipsick.
That guy, that guy did a lot of fucking damage with that wand.
Which I don't understand because it didn't look like that would do so much damage.
That was the bouncing burst.
It's this one!
There's three damage.
They must have had some kind of modifier on it.
That's what I imagine there.
Because that was just a lot of damage.
Okay, but that's fine.
Like I said, that run was already a success based on the stuff I learned.
Hey, nice!
We got some digging capability now.
Let's not waste that capability.
You know what?
I should make it a habit to go to the right first and then left.
And the reason is, if I do want to end up draining the cave, I will need a lot of stuff for it.
So maybe you explore the right side first to find that potential stuff that will allow you to do that.
When you finally get there.
So I'm going to start clearing the right side first.
Always.
Why is everything shaking?
There's bombs going off somewhere all the time.
Hello?
Where?
Is it you?
Okay, that works.
Give me the gold.
What is that?
Oh, is that the remains?
Also, snow potion.
How about we get rid of that, huh?
Can I drink it?
Brain freeze.
Wait.
Okay, it looked like it wasn't emptying, but it's just because the color of it is the same as the cuddle of the bottle is weird.
Make a big snow mountain here.
Grab the water.
So what's down here?
Hold on.
It's exciting.
A little water tunnel.
That is electrified.
Why is it hanging from a wire?
Destroy the wire.
Exquisite me.
All right.
Hazard taken care of.
What is chaotic polymorphine in there?
Whoa.
Oh, shit.
Oh, he has a wand too.
What is it with these guys having wands lately?
Um, do I have anything?
You know what?
I can set traps.
Watch this.
Come over here, bitch.
I dare you.
I double dare you.
Oh, I knew that was going to happen.
Of course, it would bounce off randomly and hit my traps.
I saw that coming a mile away.
Come here.
Or maybe I just water him a bit.
What?
Oh, I'm an idiot.
Fuck me, man.
Do not go close to those crystals because you also trigger them.
Fucking hell.
And never learn.
Do this.
And then fill up the water bottle.
Wow, that hymns didn't die from a single shot.
It was two shots it needed.
A single shot.
I need that wand.
Chaotic.
Okay.
Yeah, how about no?
Better.
I'm still going to get hit, right?
Oh, nice.
Oh, that was smooth.
Didn't get hit by it at all.
We have our nemesis up there.
No circle of stillness, no pheromone.
We do have water though.
I need a super soaker.
What's that?
Oh.
Hello.
Guys, it's time to get high in the hemisphere.
It's time to get high on that hymacy.
We're getting high.
It's going to be fun.
Let's do it.
Okay.
Eat it all.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, baby.
Oh, yeah.
Oh.
Oh, I'm tripping balls right now.
Jeez.
Acid.
Echoing and shifting.
I'm going to get that hard as well.
Oh.
Hold on.
Should I... How do I deal with that guy?
I said traps.
Doing.
Come here.
Yeah, come here.
That's it, boy.
You got to be dead soon.
I refuse to believe.
Come on.
Come on, man.
Thank you.
I wonder what acid has changed into.
Bro, we match?
Hmm.
I'm trying to think what the best outcome could be.
For the acid here.
Probably water, right?
Imagine that.
That would be insanity.
Something up there?
Man, I want the all-seeing eye.
I think I underestimated that spell for the longest time.
Uh-oh.
Mix it up.
Grab some more water.
Can I fill my pouch with water?
Wait, what is in here now?
Wait a minute.
Coal.
I guess I must have caught a stray coal.
In my death bag.
This is not very systematic exploration.
But, hold on.
Is there a...
Has a worm been here?
This looks like the work of a worm.
Like, look at these dicks here.
I feel like some kind of animal tracker.
Look at these prints.
A worm has been here.
Empty potion.
Hmm.
I mean, sure.
Well...
Ah!
Wait a minute!
It's whiskey time, he thinks.
Or is it oil?
Last time it was oil.
Yeah, look at the worm here.
There's a worm.
Oh, no.
The gods.
We need to find that worm.
Oh, no!
Where has it gone off to?
You scared me there.
Oh, nice!
Man, look at the barneys up there.
What do you call a group of barneys?
A gaggle.
I'm gonna...
I can get through there.
I actually never mind, I can just walk around.
Never mind.
Is that whiskey?
It is.
Wait, how did he die?
Toxic sludge?
I should be careful of these bouncing bursts, accidentally jumping around and hitting that barrel.
Okay.
Let me go further up.
I need to find some oil.
Last time they were showing some kind of liquid close by as an indicator.
So let me go find that.
If it is in fact there.
Oh, this is dead end.
Dude, I just got an idea.
I can carry this shit around.
Remember that...
glowy rock with the gravitational field?
This is my new weapon now.
Hold on.
Where the fuck did I come from?
How did I get down here?
I don't understand.
The layout here.
I could've...
Did I come from here?
Oh, I did.
Okay, never mind.
Ah, here it is, here it is.
Look, look, look.
Yep.
That is definitely oil.
So we need to fill this with oil.
What if I take the oil from here and put it there?
Unless they both need to be filled with oil.
Hmm.
Interesting.
Kind of want to try and grab the oil from there just to see.
If it doesn't work, I put it back.
I'm going to make a hole here.
Sweet.
Empty potion.
Let's make a hole there.
Do not catch that oil on fire, please.
Good thing that we just found an empty potion.
Yes, yes.
Let's see.
Oops.
Oh my God, I'm slippery.
Ah, okay, fine.
Just sit here.
Is it going to be enough?
Yes!
Cool.
Critical on wet enemies.
I feel like that's a good one.
Enemies are often wet, no?
Freeze charge.
Ooh.
That could be really nice against the fire people down here.
I like it.
Unfortunately, it's a shuffle wand.
That sucks.
I want to replace this because this is a shitty wand.
This is actually a decent wand.
Thanks.
Is that freeze charge going to hurt me, I wonder?
Like, it only randomly happens.
It's shuffle, right?
So...
Sometimes it's going to have a freeze charge on it.
Sometimes it won't.
I have a feeling that worm may have died.
Because where is it, right?
Nowhere to be seen.
But I haven't seen worm blood, so...
Oh, what the...
He was transformed.
What the hell?
Water myself.
Immune to fire.
Okay.
Man, I want to get in there.
I feel like...
That could be a heart hiding in that toxic sludge, you know?
But I wouldn't know, because I can't see it.
I have FOMO!
Or that sort of thing.
What's that?
Devatation.
I don't mind if I do.
Thank you.
Okay, portal here.
No enemies.
Whoa!
Thought it was shooting at me.
Uh...
I may just leave.
Actually, hold on.
Hey, sir!
No!
We didn't have enough...
Speed.
Momentum.
Oh, no.
Please don't kill me.
Oh...
I feel like it may be a good idea to just leave right now.
But...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're leaving, we're leaving.
Maybe we'll kill this Hamis, and that's it.
We have 400 monies.
That's a decent amount of dough.
Let's do it, let's leave.
Let's leave.
Plate safe.
Let's see what we got here.
What is that one?
Sea of water.
Yeah.
And that is explosion.
And that is, I don't remember if this is a modifier?
Or what exactly that is?
Toxic immunity?
Fire immunity.
Oh, no, I don't know what to pick.
I think it's fire.
We gotta go with the fire.
Toxic would also be nice.
God, I wish I could have both.
Imagine.
Imagine that.
I will take that.
That one.
This one.
I don't know what else, honestly.
Let's see my ones here.
0.22, I need something fast.
That's nice.
That's not bad.
That's like, decent.
Powerful explosion, 68 damage.
I could put that at the end of a spark bolt with trigger.
And I could use it as a...
I guess a...
What do you call it?
A missile launcher.
It's not, shuffle, let's just be sure.
Okay, let's see.
What?
Oh, I don't have enough mana.
I see.
This one, though, will work.
Beautiful.
Wait.
Oh, it's infinite!
First, oh, okay, I was so...
Okay, this is what happened.
I went over here, I looked at it, and I saw the 40.
Of course, that's the price.
But I thought, oh, there's only 40 charges on it.
So that's why I put it down here as if a...
Oh, I can dig with this, you know.
It's a missile launcher I can use occasionally.
But no, that's legit.
That's legit, dude.
That is awesome, then.
Very cool.
And let's see here.
We can even do...
What if we do a freeze charge on this as well?
What the hell?
What's that gonna look like?
Wait, is that gonna affect this one or that one?
It's this one, right?
Let's see.
What if I do this?
Oh, then it's only gonna shoot...
No, then it's gonna shoot this one with this modifier on it.
I don't think that makes a difference.
It does add a little bit of damage, I guess.
Maybe that will...
So here's the thing.
What is the downside to an explosion?
Fire.
Oh, but wait, we're fire immune!
Fuck that shit!
We're immune to fire!
Hey!
Oh, don't throw that away.
Let's make a nice digging wand.
Dig, dig, dig, digging wand.
Diggy, diggy, diggy, diggy, diggy wand.
Is this wand even useful in any way?
Doesn't look like it's very good.
Maybe this is the best we've got right now.
That's fine.
Um, do I want to do anything else?
Let's think.
This one is definitely limited, yeah.
This one, no...
Return.
After a period of time, you'll be returned to where your cast is.
You know what?
Let's have some fun with that.
So if I go...
So that's quite a decent amount of time.
I could theoretically...
Jump through a portal, grab the health, and get back.
Right?
If I'm fast enough?
We could make some funny stuff happen with that.
That is kind of crazy.
Hold on, what else can I do with this?
Let's think.
What would be the insane use case for this?
I could maybe...
I could...
I could cast this.
I could drink...
Not polymorphine, I could drink...
Teleportation.
Get somewhere, and if I don't like it, I come back.
That's another thing I could do.
Huh...
Yeah.
What if I were to...
Hold on.
Let me think.
No, that's fine.
Are we good?
We healed?
We did all that?
Nice.
Let's go.
Okay, man.
Cold pits, here we go.
And I have this.
Sort of a fast one, then I have this.
Which explodes in a lot of damage.
Cool!
And look at that bomb, it's all rusted on the outside, because it's been in the water.
And this contains grass.
Can I smoke it?
Now I can throw it.
Why is this... Okay, now it's empty.
Weird that I can collect grass.
Like, what is the point of that?
I do wonder...
What's that?
A water barrel?
I don't think I've ever seen that.
What the hell?
Isn't that weird?
Oh, but dude, look at this!
Oh my god!
Fire immunity is wild!
Like, I know it sounds wild, but it's even more wild when you experience it.
170-something!
How?
Is that...
3 damage?
Plus 68.
No, I must have read that wrong.
There's no way that was 100-something damage there.
You also have a good mixing wand now.
I am going to instinctively avoid fire still.
It's just going to happen.
I can't let go of that feeling, you know?
And I think it's a good thing not to let go of anyway.
Because you don't want to get used to being in fire for the later runs, you know?
What's with these water barrels?
Why are there so many of them?
This is weird!
Wait a minute...
I think I know what happened!
Remember we got high?
With a fun guy?
I think... Oh, never mind.
Never mind.
I thought all of these were turned into water barrels.
I thought acid actually got turned into water, and that's why all of these were those.
But now I'm... Never mind.
Whoops.
That's not what happened, I guess.
I do want to... Oh, actually, speaking of, we can chest this right now.
What is in these barrels, then?
What has acid become?
There's acid in here, right?
No, wait, there's toxic sludge in there.
Oh, never mind.
We got to find one of those enemies that bleed acid.
Let's explore the top parts first.
This guy... No, this guy bleeds toxic, I think.
Yeah.
He's basically a sewer monster.
That's what he is.
Oh, I have to remember, I don't have melee immunity here.
So maybe don't go in here, actually.
Yeah, you know what?
Let's...
Let's not go in there.
We explore the rest first, maybe we find something nice, you know?
And then...
And then we go.
I don't mind these water barrels.
In fact, I love them.
I love that they're here.
More water is only good.
Aha!
Slime mist?
No.
I refute the slime mist wand.
That's right.
Whoa!
Hold on, am I immune to these attacks as well?
I feel like I should have tested that.
I'm definitely not immune to explosive damage, that's the thing.
All right, I'm going to test it for science.
Nope, that was a bit of an explosive effect there.
I had 160 HP, now I have 154.
Also, I saw the explosion happen.
With my own eyes.
Good to know, though.
Good to know.
We get smarter every day.
Yeah, everyone, this is me destined.
That could be interesting to try at the end of a spark bolt with trigger, couldn't it?
It does say, explodes after a short time.
So...
I like it.
Do I like it?
No.
You know what, I'm going to be experimenting with new things.
Don't stick to your normal stuff, we're experimenting today.
Lots of experimentation.
I want to try and see if I can't extract the potential of all the spells.
Okay, go this way now.
I'm probably going to enter the fungal caverns here at some point.
Something satisfying about killing those guys with explosions.
Just because...
Oh, I don't have melee immunity.
Ah, there's a...
Oh, no.
Ah, kill them all.
0.12, 0.5.
That's...
Oh, spells per cast two, I hate that.
Nope.
How fast does this shoot?
Wait, not that fast.
Oh, I hate when you run out of levitation.
Gather them all up.
Oh, no.
Nice.
Did I try this?
I did.
Nice, nice, nice.
Oh, wait, I hear...
electric.
Where?
I hear you.
Something's going on in there.
No, nothing's going on in there.
I wand!
Hello, that's a sick wand.
Bunch of cool spells on it.
Let's grab it.
You know, if I see something like this, I gotta grab it.
Actually, we could replace this one.
I feel like this is better, right?
Yeah, let's just do that.
Let's not put this here, just so we don't confuse ourselves.
Let's put this as number one.
Just remember, this is a bad wand to cast.
Don't cast that wand.
Don't touch two or three.
Only one.
Only Nomero Uno.
There's a wand in there.
Decent digging, too.
Ah, nice.
Kinda want to replace this.
I mean, there is potential in the return spell.
But it's very situational, isn't it?
Like, when would I like to just go heal and come back, you know?
It's not that often.
I don't think.
Also, this one has a name, Rosu.
Oh, Rose, I guess.
I think I found this one before, then.
This exact one.
I want to replace this one, because I like this spell more.
I know I said we were going to experiment, but not at the cost of making things worse for myself.
When I see a clear opportunity for something nice, I'm going to take it, of course.
It's only if nothing else makes sense.
Come here.
Ah, sweet.
That was directed.
I do, like, 70 damage per shot.
That's pretty good.
Imagine if I find explosion immunity now, guys.
And I make this wand shoot super fast.
Explosion, I'm immune to fire, explosion, I'm unstoppable.
Imagine that.
That would be the dream.
Have I been here?
No, no!
Phew, okay.
I ran out of levitation.
Come on.
That was a bit of a disaster.
Oh.
Ooh.
Ah.
Hmm.
Nah.
It was enticing, though, with all the... with so many of them, so...
What?
Oh, never mind.
It's because I have explosion.
I thought the water barrel just exploded when I shot it.
I'm a dummy.
Aha!
A wand for me?
With an explosive box.
Yo, that wand is... not bad.
Look at that.
Thousand mana?
0.02 cast delay?
Shitty mana charge speed, though.
And only two slots.
Hmm.
I don't know.
Don't think it's worth it.
But it was cool.
For a second there.
Also, something's blowing up down there.
I can see the outline of the cave.
Wait.
Do I have better digging?
In fact, maybe I do.
Oh, that's a bit dangerous.
Should I be doing this?
No, hold on.
I have a better idea.
Nope.
I can't dig through that.
Ooh.
Whoop!
I heard him.
This barrel just moved on its... on its own.
Phew.
But you hear that shotgun?
Panic strikes.
Oh, almost killed myself.
All right, I'm immune.
Thank you.
Let's get in here.
All right, nothing in there.
It feels so surreal to walk through fire, you know?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I hit myself there.
That's the danger of this explosive thing.
Close quarters with this is a little sketchy.
Okay, we're at the edge now.
Oh, hello.
Let's be careful here.
Nice.
Whoa!
That guy just killed himself with this.
That was about to be real scary for me.
Giga disc.
No, those are way too scary.
I do wonder if I have melee immunity and I cast these, am I immune?
That could be a, that could be a real build.
This has to be melee damage, right?
So I can throw these anywhere with no fear.
Ideas.
The wand is not bad.
Although it is.
Very low mana max.
But very high mana charge speed.
Could be cool.
Maybe I do want to replace this.
Yeah, fuck the return.
I don't see, I like, I see some use cases for it, but not something that immediately makes me go, oh wow, I need to be able to do that.
You know?
What's up here?
There's something up there.
Look, oh, you can even see the outline when you do the explosion.
This shit's gonna explode.
That's a lot of explosives up there.
Oh, come on.
Here we go.
And there it is.
Dead end.
Wait.
I guess there's nothing there.
I want all seeing eye.
But the cool thing about the explosion is, it gives you a brief glimpse.
Inside a wall, you know?
It's enough to make you think, is it worth it or not to keep digging?
Like here, is there something in there?
Not really.
Actually, really nice.
I've been here, I think.
No.
Yeah, maybe.
Something in there?
Yes.
We gotta fix up the world.
Oh, very nice.
Beautiful.
Love seeing that stuff.
Wait, was there?
Oh, okay.
I thought I saw another heart.
Whoa!
Wow!
This dude is very immune to explosions.
Also, he's throwing random potions.
Anything here?
A bit of gold.
800 gold, not bad.
I feel like I'm doing great on the second level here.
We had to leave a bit prematurely in the first, but...
it is what it is.
This fire immunity has...
something going for it, doesn't it?
I feel like it's giving me great potential.
That's a chest!
Damn!
Very nice.
That's a lot.
I do not know if I've been...
on this side over here.
I guess I have.
Question is though, should we go into fungal caverns?
We could peek inside real quick.
You know, just in case there's a heart right at the edge somewhere and we can grab it.
And if it looks like it's a bad idea, then it's time to get out.
That's the plan.
If I even smell...
problems coming, then I'm out of there.
Wait, did I try that one?
I must have, because I've been here.
Yes, it's that one.
Okay.
That was that one.
Fungus, here we go.
This is it.
Wait, what's that?
Ambruh!
Dude, I'm glad we came here.
Levitation.
I get rid of this empty pouch, I think.
Oh, you know what?
I could collect fungi with that.
I just picked up some moss.
Huh.
Maybe I get rid of...
Actually, I wanted to test this on the enemies.
So, you know what?
Let's get rid of the levitation.
Yeah, fuck it.
I want this.
And there's a wand right here.
See, this place is a nightmare for this wand I have right now, the explosive wand.
Lots of narrow places...
Oh, no.
Yeah, and this guy...
Yeah, you know what?
Let's not...
I'm gonna check out what this wand is, and then I'm out of there.
That's it.
I'm not gonna stay.
Just wanna see what's in that wand.
That is all.
Can I get to it easily?
I think...
Oh, nice!
Fuck yeah!
Oh, that's not bad!
I like it!
Maybe I get that instead of this?
No, wait, this wand is better, I think.
Yeah, fuck the triplicate.
Also, there's another one right there.
Oh, man.
I really should leave, but...
Come on, man!
Maybe I shouldn't yet.
Just a quick peek.
How do I get in there quickly?
Maybe I don't get in there quickly.
Unless...
Glowing lands!
Thanks!
See, now I could have used the...
No, I could not.
I was about to say I could have used the return spell here, but I can't.
Oh my god, what's happening down there?
Guys, I didn't mean to go in here.
Now I'm stuck in here.
This has become a...
This is no longer exploration.
This is getting our hide out of this place in one piece situation.
Okay, that's a shitty wand.
What's this?
Polymorphine?
No, thanks.
Uh-oh.
I guess we go right.
Oh no, oh no, oh no.
No!
Oh, man.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
How do I kill him?
I don't know how to kill him!
I'm stuck, I'm stuck, I'm stuck!
Ah!
He's tickling me!
Tickling me to death.
Oh my...
Get out of here, man!
I'm actually gonna die in here, guys.
It's real, I'm dying.
We're leaving!
Come on!
Run, run, run, run, run, run, run!
What's that?
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know.
We're leaving, we're leaving, we're leaving, we're leaving!
Leave me alone!
Fuck off!
Nice, nice.
Is he after me?
Wow, that was scary.
That's what happens when you go in the fungal caverns.
Shit happens.
Quite a lot.
Why is there so little water in that?
Teleport, very cool.
What's this one?
Water?
Oh my god.
Lightning bolt.
That is sweet.
Protectiles near you, slow down.
No, no.
Reroll.
Repulsion field.
Telekinetic kick.
I'm tempted, but no.
Living on the edge.
Forty steps, phasing.
Bro, I don't like any of these.
Fuck's sake.
We're gonna come back here and reroll later.
Yep.
Take that one.
And what else?
Let's see.
I think that is it.
Maybe water could be cool to have.
Why is it green?
Oh, it's a material.
I just fucking realized.
Modifiers are blue.
Projectiles are red.
How come I never thought about the colors?
Huh.
Well, that explains a lot.
Very cool.
Let's do...
Ooh, I could all...
Ooh, glowing lance though.
I gotta go with lightning bolt.
Charge speed is quite shit on that.
This one is better.
Although it shoots two spells at a time.
I don't enjoy that.
Hold on.
Let me try this.
Here.
We're gonna experiment like I said.
Okay.
Pretty cool.
But honestly, kind of an inferior version of this.
No?
The castelay is bad on that.
Like the fact that it's gonna explode after a certain amount of time.
I don't like that.
This could be cool to have together with water.
No?
Wait, what?
That's not a lot of water coming out of that.
But actually, it reduces castelay and recharge time.
Isn't that interesting?
What if I do that?
Dump, dump, dump.
Oh, wow!
Like a mini chainsaw, in a way.
I can dig it.
Sparkly bounce, no thank you.
This one is nice to have.
These ones don't care for them that much.
Neither do I care for that.
Not really that one either.
The rest, this can go away.
Maybe this one can go away as well.
Okay.
Let's see if I can't make something.
I think the best prospect for a good one is this one.
It has a large recharge time, that's the issue.
Do I have a double or something?
I do, I do have a double.
So if I do, hold on.
Let me see the board.
Shoot, double, so it shoots that one and another one.
So what if I do this?
Then it shoots...
I guess this counts as a projectile as well, even though it's not.
So let me do this one.
Always drips a bit of water.
And it drips it where I shoot it.
What am I limited by here?
It's recharge time.
But we have this.
It's not going to remove it entirely though, that's a lot of recharge.
I mean, we can try.
Whoops.
Better.
Definitely better.
What else we got that can do something like that.
I do like the water on it.
What if I put this outside of it?
Aha!
I wonder why that is.
Hold on.
So it shoots this.
Okay.
I mean, it's kind of shit, but...
Yeah, we run out of mana quick with that one.
But hear me out.
It's not shuffle, it shoots two at a time.
So let's remember that.
Two at a time.
So it's going to shoot...
that one.
Let's see.
Recharge time is the bottleneck that's expected here.
Because the recharge time is quite high on this wand.
Hmm.
That wand is actually kind of sick.
Wait, no, it's not.
The castor lay is sick, though.
I feel like I'm just going to go with my lightning bolts.
My trusty lightning bolts.
That's a solid wand right there.
That's a good wand.
Maybe I'll even put it on a...
shuffle.
Just because it doesn't matter.
Yeah, that's cool.
I like it.
Main damage wand, then we have this one as well.
For those more long range situations.
Or...
No, that's fine.
I like it.
And then we have a teleport.
And then we're going to have some bombs, I guess.
Because why not?
That seems fine to me.
What if I put freeze charge on...
this one as well, huh?
Sure, let's go with that.
That seems fun.
I like it.
And then we're going to come back here later.
And then we're going to grab the remaining.
Oh, I have to be careful.
I'm not electricity immune, so I almost just jumped in the water with this wand.
Also, I need to use this as my... I think I'm...
I may have that as my primary.
Is that a bad idea?
No, I'm going to have electricity because that's what my muscle memory tells me.
And then we can have that one on...
a three.
Number two is always teleport for me.
There we go.
Alright, we're packing it, baby.
Let's go.
Oh, it needs to be on four.
I need to...
Okay, yeah.
Weird fungus pouch.
Oh, yeah.
Throw this away, then.
Thanks.
We could get high again.
You know what?
Let's do it.
Whoa!
Was he aiming for the rat?
Get out of here.
Where's my guy?
Oh, he died?
No, wait.
There's someone else.
This is my long range.
The electricity wand is my medium range.
Wait, why did he just get blown off into space?
That's not normal.
Is that because of the freeze charge?
What the hell is happening here?
I feel like it's good because I didn't think about this.
This also phrases the enemies, right?
So, when I hit them, I can stunlock them, I guess.
I'm starting to like the freeze charge.
Someone with a wand.
Where are you?
There you are.
It's one of these guys again.
Oh, shit.
There we go.
Your shenanigans are done.
No more.
See the wand?
That is a decent stat wand, even though there's only two slots on it.
In fact, I'll just replace this one, I think.
Uh, yeah.
Why the hell not?
Neat.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wrong wand.
Block?
What do you mean?
Oh, man.
Fire immunity is going to be so important in Heezy Base as well.
When all the mechanical enemies explode, you know, they release oil and everything gets set on fire.
Ah!
Los Wandos!
And a double!
Ooh!
Maybe I'll... You know what?
Two slots is not actually great.
Even though the wand is nice, it's kind of useless later on.
Let's take that instead.
I like it.
Whoops.
Wrong wand again.
I need to fucking make sure I have the right wand equipped.
I didn't hurt myself with it this time though, but it was close.
Wait, I'm freezing and exploding at the same time.
It's a bit confusing there.
Hello?
Wait, is that freezing the water and then exploding at the surface of the water?
Is that what's happening?
That's why I can never get there.
Oh, that's annoying.
That's a fun little interaction between those two spells.
I'm not afraid of fire.
I'm afraid of bullets though!
Bullets.
My only weakness.
Oh, yeah?
Fuck you.
Thinking you can snipe me.
I reject that proposition.
Wait, is that a worm?
That looks wormy to me.
Is that the same worm?
It's been on the loose this entire time.
Look, this is definitely the work of a worm.
It is hanging out here somewhere.
When I find it, I'll kill it.
Oh, hello there.
Loki's frozen.
So cool.
Actually a cool combo here.
Ah, wrong wand!
Why do I switch?
I think I switched to number one just because of habit.
You know, that's my damage wand usually.
There you are.
Oh, you have a lot of HP.
Oh, God, this is going to be an issue, isn't it?
How do I probably deal with you?
Oh, you're frozen now?
Look at all the HP he has!
That is a big guy!
I may actually just die here.
What do I have?
I don't have shit.
Also, I have teleport after I remember that.
I don't like this.
I do not like this.
This is bad.
Wait, is this guy immune to explosion or something?
Why does he take so little damage?
Sir?
I'm scared of following him.
Oh, man.
He's killing enemies.
That's something, I guess.
He's going to anger the gods, though!
This motherfucker!
He's going to ruin my run.
Where'd he go?
There he is.
Oh, wait!
Losing HP!
He's kind of low!
I can get him.
I'm the worm hunter, bitch.
No, don't fall in the portal, don't fall in the portal.
Hold on, kill that guy.
Kill that guy.
And that guy.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Whoa!
Oh, man, he's digging a lot.
Am I hurting him?
He seems weak now.
Oh!
Come back here.
I got you!
That's right!
I wonder if I can't get any worm blood, because he's frozen.
It's become ice, look at that!
Incredible.
Wow.
Look at these tunnels it made.
I do wonder if he somehow angered the gods, and that message will only trigger when I enter the next holy mountain or something.
Because he's been digging so much, and I know he's been digging in the coal pits, too.
So, he must have gotten down here somehow, right?
That scares me right now.
Invisiblium.
You know what, let's get high, and then we grab the Invisiblium.
This is the plan.
It's time for the second high session.
Look at this massive fungus that I'm growing.
Why is it so slow?
Oh, I think it's because I'm also picking it up when I walk over it with the pouch.
I've got to be careful not to walk over it.
Okay, here we go.
Look how fast I get high.
Tripping balls.
I wonder what the percentage is.
Show me!
No!
It's over.
Guys.
Water has become poison.
So, you know what?
This is like Romeo and Juliet.
Let me do my best impression.
Wait, what?
Wait, you can't die from poison?
No way.
I take my own life.
Well, okay.
But now I haven't confirmed at least how that system works.
So when it says...
You hear the word poison.
Shifting or whatever.
What it means is that something has become poison.
It doesn't mean poison has become something.
So, I actually was so confused for the longest time about that.
So now at least that one's put to bed.
You know?
That's nice.
That was a fun run though.
That was actually really cool.
Lava potion?
Nah, I don't want lava potion.
That seems like a bad idea.
Also, I have a feeling there's something up there.
Can I get an outline of something?
Funny?
Okay.
No, no.
I have three bombs to my name.
Use them wisely.
Ah!
I will use them now.
Shit, I could have gone in there without.
Why did I do it?
See, I should have tried that first.
I did not use them wisely.
What do we have here?
Okay, I was about to use a bomb again, but then I thought more about it and I decided not to.
Hello.
Got a shoddy.
It's actually a decent spell.
This, uh...
Spitterbolt.
Anything here?
Nope.
All quiet on the western front, or eastern front I guess this is.
Return to sender.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
Hey.
And he did.
He did.
Whoa!
Guys, holy crap!
Calm down, calm down, calm down, calm down, calm down.
Wow, I was not prepared for that.
I'm gonna leave him.
Or will I?
Yes, I will.
I come back later with a Super Soaker.
You know what?
Let me water them.
Yeah, you hate that!
Yeah, you like that?
You like that?
Oh, that feels good.
Killed them both.
Easily.
Don't mess with me.
Oh yeah.
You know what?
Let me try this now.
I never get to try it.
Let's see how effective this is.
I swear I'm gonna use it on the next one I see.
I will use combat focus next time.
Only some of you are gonna get that one.
Grab some water.
You!
Let's see how much damage I do.
Boink!
Fuck!
Alright, fine.
I'll try it next time.
Ah!
Look at that!
Did you see what I saw?
Hold on.
We need to bomb our way in.
Right here.
Fire in the hole!
Say what?
It's gonna get destroyed now.
Thank you!
I have to remember, I'm not immune to fire.
Not anymore.
That was a nice perk to have, though.
Feels good to finally have tried it.
Okay, watch this.
Damn it!
Oh my god!
Okay, it's not worth it to try and kill them with those things, man.
This is just...
Okay, here we go, here we go.
Hey!
That was not bad.
52 damage?
Hold on.
Hey!
Yo, this is actually kind of legit.
If you get good at this, you can...
Look at that!
Okay, that only did 18, but it didn't have a lot of momentum.
Oh my god, it fell on them, too!
Not bad!
That's a decent amount.
It's basically like a rock.
You know, when you have homing rock, except you have to home it yourself.
You have to give it that extra push.
But I guess it's the same principle there.
Rain cloud.
Thanks.
Oh, thanks for destroying that for me, bro.
Watch this.
That is legit!
You lie and wait with it.
Someone comes around the corner and you're like...
Ambrosia!
Um... I can get in there.
In fact...
Wait a minute.
I'm being super efficient here.
Or no, actually, hold on.
Use this one.
Oh, don't kick the fire!
Damn it!
Nah, you know what?
Fuck it, I'm gonna use a bomb.
I'm too lazy!
Nope, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay, fine.
Nice!
Ambrosia acquired.
Now I will go down street and turn corner.
And kill everyone.
Ah, Barney's up there.
What is going on here?
Doesn't that look weird?
I feel like something's going on there.
I've seen that before.
Hmm...
Intriguing.
You!
Hey, you want this?
Okay, you don't want that.
That's fine.
Maybe your friends want it.
What's this?
Hey, that's not a bad want, except shuffle.
Oh, that's sick.
That's not bad at all.
Me likey likey.
Crikey crikey.
Wait, crikey is something you say when...
No, craiks is something you say when things go wrong.
That's the expression.
I wanna swim.
Little air pocket.
Hey, Barney.
This is for you.
Alright, nevermind.
Hey, you.
It's actually insane.
Oh!
Bastard!
Wait, these are the exact same stats again.
What the hell are the chances?
Look.
That's so weird.
Yo, that's a sick one.
What the hell?
Um, can I get in there, please?
Whiskey!
Thanks.
Ah, okay, okay, watch, watch, watch this.
I need to get up there.
Hey, come here.
Holy shit!
Yo, the tablet is wild.
You roll it down a hill and it just kills them.
Because of the momentum.
I have found a new way to deal with these guys.
Fuck the circle of stillness.
Fuck the pheromone.
Fuck the water.
It's tablet time, baby.
Okay, then.
Speaking of pheromone, wow.
Get rid of whiskey.
Grab this.
We need that later.
That's actually such a cool feeling in this game, you know?
You have this knowledge now and you're like, oh yeah.
I find a broken wand.
I'm going to keep that until that part, you know?
Or, oh, I have pheromone.
I can potentially use that later on in that part.
You know, because of the healers and all that.
It's cool!
Impromptu Hamus Massacre.
Let me go around here.
This one is actually nuts.
If only it wasn't shuffled, then it would have been an insane-o style wand.
I've been there.
Go down here.
Go for another swim.
I can make it all the way.
Easy peasy.
I've been there.
Let's go here instead.
Aha!
Watch!
Hello!
Come on!
Okay, it didn't kill him, but it did a lot of damage to him.
Oh my god, oh my god!
I'm in a bad spot!
Why did I go down there?
He's still not dead, is he?
This fucker.
I need this.
He's still not...
Motherfucker!
Did he finally croak?
Looks like it.
This is the special horta.
Actually, this is just the horta.
The other guy was called...
What was it?
Heiku horta.
Wow, look at these guys, just swimming in concentrated men.
Actually, it looks really blinding.
Wow, there's a heart there.
Thanks.
Can I get up?
Oh, I can't.
Watch this.
Surprise delivery!
This is hilarious.
I'm a menace!
That's a slimy egg.
1300 gold as well, this is wild.
Crazy start.
I don't want concentrated mana.
Not right now, at least.
I can get in there.
I've been there.
I have not been down here.
Thank you.
Okay, I think it may be time for us to...
GTFO.
Yeah, let's go.
Solid place to keep going.
We did some exploring.
We have a bunch of money.
Oh, whoa.
No.
Nope.
Nice rock there.
Ah, no.
At this point, no thanks.
Always cast.
No.
Angry ghost.
You know what, guys?
I'm gonna play the long game here.
I'm gonna keep this one here.
Until I have gathered a lot of HP.
This is the long gamble here, okay?
We're long gambling.
I will come back to this bad boy late in the run.
And grab it.
Because I have faith that this is the one.
So what do I want?
I want...
None of them.
Maybe this one because of the digging capabilities there.
That wouldn't be too bad.
I like that.
Let's get this one.
And then we can basically just...
Wait, why is that showing a damage number?
What?
That's...
Wait, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Why are they exploding and...
Oh, it always casts some kind of bullshit.
I see that now.
Hold on.
So put these up here instead.
Let's use the other wand.
I don't like that wand.
That wand scares me.
Put this one up here.
This one is decently fast.
Should be decent.
Yeah, not bad.
Although...
It costs 10 mana.
Is it better on this one?
Nah, this is fine.
Cool, now we have a digging.
And this wand, I guess, let's put the...
No, let's not put anything there.
We're gonna replace these.
This is shit wand.
This is a not shit wand, but it's like kind of shit.
Not shit.
We can replace that later.
So, are there any non-shitty wands here that I would like to bring with me?
0.02, it is kind of fast.
That's not bad either, actually.
That's not a bad wand.
0.1, 0.07.
Wait a minute.
Isn't this better if I do that?
Hold on, am I crazy?
I literally can't tell.
I feel like it's actually faster like this because now I'm reliant on recharge.
No, wait, Castellay is still gonna be dominating though.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah!
But I think this is okay.
Because if I want to replace this wand later, I still have these, you know?
This is fine.
I like it.
I like it a lot.
Okay, let's go.
Cold pits I have returned to the E.
And I am here to collect all the hearts because I have an opportunity later.
The game gave me a proposition that fell kindly on my ears.
But I'll take it later.
I just need the HP, okay?
That guy was tippy dancing around my shots.
Sweet.
Okay, okay, okay.
Also, hold on.
I died, so I need to update the thingy.
I believe we're at 72 deaths now.
Something like that.
We have to double check next time I die.
Hit me right in the face.
Sometimes I should... I'm not looking at my character like I'm aiming over here and I look at where my cursor is and I'm not really paying attention to where my character is.
That's kind of a flaw in me.
I should be able to have one... my left eye look at my character and my right eye look at where my cursor is.
That would be a trick.
I bet that would look really funny.
What is your deal?
Are you gonna damage me if you're getting close?
Is that what's happening with you?
I'm going random directions right now and I've accepted that's just how it is.
I'm not even trying to make this systematic.
It is what it is.
Oh, nice.
Hey, what?
Gold and a heart?
That's kind of crazy.
Kind of wild that there can be multiple things in a chest.
I guess the chances are quite low of that.
Oh, but watch this.
I can get in here.
Almost.
Oh no, I can get in there.
Oh man, dude.
Poland is really nice.
I mean, I knew a dog, but it's really digging.
Soft and hard materials.
All right, nothing there.
You know what?
A strategy is to sit down here and shoot them in water because their projectiles can't reach me.
That's just a strategy that just occurred to me.
That wouldn't be too bad, would it?
Can I get through here?
No, no way.
Actually, I can.
Of course I can.
Oh, no.
Scary.
Whoa.
Yo, a shop.
Wait, what is that?
Bomb cart.
I...
I need to see this.
Some is a self-propelled mine cart loaded with explosives?
Say what?
Downwards bolt.
You know what?
We're experimenting.
Spend all the money.
Fuck it.
We can find more money.
That's fine.
No, it's not.
There we go.
Why is this burning?
There's gold.
Yo, nice.
Thanks.
So the question is, do I go in here?
I probably don't go in there, huh?
Yeah, let's not go in there.
116 HP and shitty wands?
Nope.
Oh, that guy is...
I think he's ambrosia-ed up.
Sir?
Ours, thou, and moon to everything?
Kiba's kibi.
Oh, I can't.
I have no room for that.
Oh, another one.
Not bad.
That was the shortest excursion into the...
...bungle caverns ever.
Kind of want to get high.
I... I...
It's a gamble, you know?
It's a gamble.
Kind of feel like gambling.
Maybe it's bad.
To gamble all this...
...as much, you know?
Oh my god, this is...
...bad.
Oh, it wasn't that bad.
I thought I lost way more HP than I did.
We are okay.
Gave me that money.
Thanks.
Nice.
Like, look at this.
All that gold just there?
Sweet.
Wait, something's in there.
Oh, it's a man.
It's a haiku-hurta.
No, it's not.
It's a...
What are the names of the shotgun people?
Oh.
Yeah, I'm not gonna remember that.
Heilikohisi.
Sir, get away from me.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my god.
Did I get him?
No, he teleported.
He fell into the liquid.
Where did he go?
He's off somewhere.
There he is.
Oh, interesting wand he's got there.
I kind of want to murder him and take it by myself.
Bro.
Come on, man.
What an asshole.
Like, fight me, bitch.
Oh yeah, they're slightly homing.
Holy god!
They bleed lava.
I gotta remember this.
Oh god, this is...
It's kind of a disaster.
Water, water, water, water, water, water, water, water, water.
Burning trail.
Double spell, double spell is nice.
The wand is kind of bad.
But, yeah, it's kind of bad.
Nope.
Not right now.
I need to find more hearts.
This is how we get good money.
Look how easy it is.
Yes.
Track him.
Yup.
Alright, that was...
Look how much lava came out of him.
That's too much lava, man.
How is there even that much lava inside of him?
Let's go east.
The digging is nuts.
I wonder what the trick is to killing these guys without having them drop all the lava.
Maybe not make them bleed or whatever.
Oh my god, come here.
This guy won't die.
There we go.
Finally.
Hold on, I can dig here.
Huh?
I hit myself just now.
Poland is dangerous.
Hey, what's down there?
Okay.
I'm kind of rich already.
It's all thanks to this Poland.
I hate the little pixels that you don't dig, you know?
Like they block your entire path.
Maybe I'm getting too greedy here.
Nah.
Can't get too greedy.
Let's go this way.
Ouch, I hit myself again.
Also, this is bad.
Yeah, let's... I think we should leave.
It's time.
It is time.
What have we got?
That's kind of cool.
That's also kind of cool.
Not cool.
Very not cool.
That's cool.
That's really cool.
But...
Is it cool enough?
Hmm...
Fly faster, lower... I mean, that is nice.
I like it a lot.
It is quite sick.
Let's see if we can make something out of this.
Now that one adds a lot of cast delay.
Gives some damage.
Plus five explosive damage.
I mean, that's cool.
But this is shuffle, so that's kind of a problem.
That's really nice.
This one right here.
Yes, how about we do that?
Why is that so slow?
I guess recharge time, huh?
But isn't it?
Oh, it's because of this.
Now this one...
Let's separate into a bundle of five explosive bolts as soon as it moves downwards.
Let's see it.
Ah...
I see.
Huh.
Not very, maybe more effective on this one then.
Sorry, how much damage?
100 something?
That's kind of sick.
Cost a lot of mana though.
90 mana.
Costly.
I don't know about that.
Let's see what else we got.
These are pretty cool.
I like these.
Concentrated lights.
Okay, let's put them down here.
Yo...
I think I like it.
That's pretty cool.
Can it get better though?
Maybe add a little bit of...
this one to that?
No, this is shuffle.
How does that look?
Bad.
I think I want this.
I mean, that's dope.
Me likey.
That's my wand.
We found our wand.
All of these can go on the floor because I don't care for them.
This will remain my digging wand.
And then we should have a...
We could have a rain wand maybe.
No, black hole of course.
Black hole on that one.
And then we can have...
TNT maybe?
Or rain.
Let's think, where are we going?
We're going to the snowy depths.
Snowy depths.
Probably TNT is nice there.
Let's get through obstacles.
Yeah.
That seems cool.
I could also try this on one of these.
Well, maybe...
one of these.
Ah, not enough mana?
Crap.
Unless...
Ah, I don't have mana for black hole on that one then.
Damn it.
Nah, you know what?
This is fine.
Black hole here.
And then we have a shitty wand that we want to replace.
That seems good to me.
We can put some dynamite in here.
Why not?
That seems good.
Let's go.
Oh yeah!
Feels like a proper machine giver.
Machine and giver.
That's why I don't feel sick.
Oh no.
Really pushes them back, huh?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa.
Dodging projectiles all over the place.
Are they bouncing?
Maybe a bit.
Oh yeah, they are.
Depends on the angle of attack.
Oh nice, my favorite track.
Okay!
Glowing lands?
What's that?
Anti-homing!
Why... would I do that?
Hello?
Chaotic path?
Causes a projectile to chaotically fly wherever it wishes.
I mean...
No.
That seems really bad.
In every conceivable way.
Am I crazy?
But the wand itself is kinda nice.
It has a lot of stuff on it.
I'll take it for now.
Okay, this pinpoint of light is not exactly doing a lot of damage.
I gotta be honest here.
It's also wildly inaccurate.
Or is that because of the wand?
No, I don't know.
That's odd.
I mean, it's okay, you know?
It's just not anything to ride home about.
Can I at least get through here?
Yeah.
Nice.
We've got ghostbusters on the move.
And those guys, too.
Nice.
Oh, oh, wait, what?
Oh, this sets things on fire?
Oh, that's cool.
I have no idea.
I guess the pinpoint of light is like a laser.
It gets hot, I guess.
Very neat.
And then we've got a wand here, nice.
Well, wait a minute, this is steel, but we have black holes!
So we don't care at all.
Just to confirm.
Doesn't work.
What's this?
Yo, that wand is good!
That's a really good wand!
Maybe I'll say fuck the Poland.
Yeah, thanks.
What am I hearing?
Someone is treading water, it sounds like.
Uh-oh, there's a lot of stuff happening here.
I'm being kind of surrounded here.
Let's be careful.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Where?
Where are you?
Shit, I gotta get the other way.
Got him.
Wand.
I need it.
And now I kind of want my digging wand.
But this works.
Is there an easier way in or do I have to black hole it?
Do I even have enough?
I have one more black hole.
Okay, so this is rock.
I mean...
Sure.
I'm gonna black hole, I guess.
Uh, cover myself?
Yeah.
Oh no.
Okay, I can get in.
What the hell, explosive detonator?
All nearby explosive spells cast by you instantly detonate.
Uh...
Isn't this kind of a death trap?
That one's gonna instantly explode?
No.
I'm gonna say no to that one.
I'm losing way too much HP.
This is a crazy wand.
Oh, I forgot about you!
I forgot about you!
I thought you died.
I had completely faced you out of my mind.
It's time to move on, I think.
Unfortunately, it is what it is, man, but...
Fuck the black hole.
It's empty.
Oh, man.
Ah, 13 HP.
We gotta go.
We gotta go out.
Where's the nearest... Here it is.
Go.
Just go, man.
It's not going too great here.
Never mind.
It's going fabulously.
Holy shit.
All right.
What do we have down here?
Give me something good.
Oh, no.
I don't think there's anything good here.
I'm gonna re-roll.
What's that?
Electricity?
You're immune to electric damage.
But metal and liquids around you electrify constantly.
Look out.
Why should I look out if it's electric?
If I'm immune.
Hmm.
I don't... No.
I don't like it.
Repelling cape?
Shit.
Guys, I don't like any of these.
I mean, this could be nice.
You know what?
This could be really nice in combination with the perk that gives you damage absorption.
When you don't have stains on you.
You know what?
Sure.
Let's try that.
Let's go with that.
And then I'm gonna buy this one.
Oh, I don't even have money for that.
Oh, crap.
Okay.
It's that expensive.
Damn.
I mean, I guess I found a lot of stuff here to experiment with.
I don't know what to keep.
I guess I could just leave stuff on this wand.
I like this one.
I like that one.
Summon missile?
A missile!
I mean...
No.
Anti-homing, definitely not.
Okay, you know what's cool about this one?
You could combine this with a...
one of those Giga disc projectiles.
So that they come to you and then they instantly get sliced by that.
Right?
That could be a thing.
Get rid of that.
Rid of that one.
We can keep this one.
We can also keep this one, I guess.
This is shuffled.
That's bad.
This is a good wand.
Actually, really good.
Holy shit.
Yo!
Can we not make something out of this?
I want...
this, I think.
Man, I... Oh, but wait, I have mana.
Wait, where is it?
No, I don't!
I couldn't buy it yet.
Sheeee...
Damn it.
I'm coming back for that.
I also have to remember, I still have a perk.
In the first area, with extra health.
But I'm getting that later on, when I have a lot of HP.
If I get to a lot of HP.
For now, though...
Maybe this is fine.
We can even have something like that.
Wait, wait.
Oh, pinpointer!
Makes it shoot really fast.
That's not bad.
Even better.
Hey, that's cool.
That's cool.
I like that.
Very cool.
And we can even do something with it, no?
Can we...
We could put a homing on it.
Oh, but it's shuffle.
Hey!
Hey, that's actually really nice.
And even better, that it's short range homing.
Right?
Think about it.
You want to aim like, very precisely with this.
But only have it like, if you miss by a little bit at the end, it will correct only at the end.
Not bad, I don't think.
In fact, I like it.
This one is going to get better later.
We have to come back here, grab this one when we have the money, and then go to the next Holy Mountain to actually change it.
Bit of a detour, but...
You gotta do what you gotta do, right?
Holy shit, we're here.
This is going to be a bit of a challenge, I think.
Uh-oh.
Oh, no.
This is already not looking great, guys.
The damage here is not...
Man,
I'm burning all the time.
Oh, but you know what?
Pheromone time, babe.
Oh, here he is.
Yes!
What are the chances of me thinking about that, and then he appears right after?
Hey, let's go!
I kind of want to...
This is going to sound a little nuts, okay, but...
I want to keep him somewhere, I want to lock him in, in a little room.
Can I do that?
If I had a way to...
If I had a telekinetic kick, I could maybe block him in somewhere.
Come here.
Follow me.
That's good.
Now, tell me I can get through here.
Thank God, okay.
Oh, wait.
Don't kill him, don't kill him, don't kill him, don't kill him, don't kill him.
I want you to come up here.
Actually, I have an idea, I have an idea.
This is the way to do it.
But I need a teleport bolt for this.
Can I hit...
Fuck!
Shit, I knew that was going to happen.
But at least I know now, if they're pheromone, you still can hit them with the spell.
I just feel like that hasn't always been the case.
Like, I've had pheromone friends with me that I couldn't kill, remember?
I was trying to get rid of them because they were annoying me.
And it didn't work.
So I don't know about that, man.
Maybe it's because that spell that I was shooting...
...did no friendly damage.
But this one does.
That's possible.
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
Wrong way!
Alright, well...
That's fine.
Not bad.
Uh,
I need to water myself.
Oh my god, okay, that water disappeared quick.
Oh, and I'm out of water now!
Oh, shh!
Okay, that's fine, that's fine.
Very nice.
I think it's because I hit some oil.
Nice.
I gotta say, glowing lands for this place is actually amazing.
You just need a double glowing lands, at least.
Just so you have a bit more DPS against the mechanical enemies.
Other than that, it's great.
Whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop.
Uh, oh no!
Aaargh!
This stun is really bad.
Ouch!
Man, getting rid of these guys is a struggle right now.
But I still think the pinpoint of light is better against those enemies...
...than my glowing lands, like the mechanical.
I wanna find another healer.
Are you a healer or not a healer?
Sweet.
Come on, man, show thyself.
Uh oh.
I'm kinda stuck here.
This is a bad spot to be in!
I may die here.
It's over.
Yeah.
I was in a bad spot.
I was in this bad spot.
That was really, really tricky.
That was bad.
Okay, here's the plan.
I'm gonna take a quick break.
I'm gonna actually get some food going.
And then when that arrives, I'm gonna take another quick break to eat it.
And then I wanna keep playing this game.
This is so addicting, man.
This game is addictive.
So I'm gonna take a break, really quickly.
Like two minutes here, and then I'll be back.
And then sometime after that, I'm gonna take a little bit of a longer break.
So, uh...
I'll be right back.
Okay.
Nice.
Okay, I can...
Ooh, nice.
This is a good start.
And get up here.
In fact, I don't even need to jump up.
I can watch this.
I can shoot blindly.
I'm gonna go like this.
Come on.
One more, I believe.
What?
Ah, okay.
That was close.
I should have aimed a little more to the right.
There we go.
Hey, I'm taking that with me.
This is now a deadly weapon.
Yes, sir.
Okay.
Very good.
I had to use a lot of magic missiles there, though.
We go right first.
And I have water, perfect.
Water is good.
Mm-hmm.
Very few enemies.
Oh, hello there, Heiko Huerta.
I actually knew a guy from Finland named Heiko.
It's spelled the same way as 2Ks.
What's happening down here?
Nothing exciting.
Now that's exciting.
Grant me access.
Also, did I change the death counter here?
I think I did.
Cool.
We're at 73 deaths.
I've had them, not today, actually.
I'm not having very successful runs here.
That last death was really bad, though.
I completely fucked that one up.
I panicked a little bit.
It's much easier to get into those situations where you panic when you don't have a good want.
Because you shoot at an enemy, you don't kill him, which gives the enemy another opportunity to shoot you.
But then you shoot again, and you still don't kill him, which gives the enemy another opportunity to shoot you.
And in the meantime, you've spent all this time trying to kill him, another enemy shows up, and it all snowballs from there.
In other words, everything goes bad when you don't have a good want.
I mean, it's kind of obvious when you say it.
There's so many factors going into what happens when you have a shit want, you know?
That makes it even worse.
It's a huge snowball.
That was a nice amount of change right there.
Thanks.
Oh.
Oh, he's going to have a bad time.
Watch this.
That was actually cool.
Let's mix this up.
Get back, get back, get back.
Perk!
Ah, damn it, we lost a bunch of HP.
Wait, do these guys also die in water?
Are they made of toxic sludge, and that's why?
Oh, God, come on.
What's happening?
Switch to water, please.
Dammit.
Okay, so to get in there...
Magic missile time, I guess.
In fact, I can also hide from these guys underneath the water.
Because their projectiles will be turned into water when they hit the surface.
And I should be okay.
I think the best way in is here.
That works.
Ah, actually the wand is not bad.
Oh, wrong wand.
The wand itself is, you know, decent.
Hold on, watch this.
Come here.
Oh, he's a very annoying spot.
He's a boss.
Please die.
Nice.
Fell into a puddle and died.
We'd love to see that.
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
A burning haiku hurta.
That's a scary thing to see.
I want to find more hearts, please.
Really want to get up there.
That ain't happening.
I guess I'll just go west.
Oh yeah, that's a wand.
Nice.
Ah.
I think I like it.
Damn.
Open up.
Close quarter, this is really good.
What's that?
Purifying powder.
Weirdly enough, that can also go in a bottle.
I had that in a bottle last time.
Uh, hold on.
Okay, that's not going to do anything.
Oh no.
Oh, we're fine.
Okay.
This could have been worse.
For sure.
Thank you.
Ha ha.
Another boulder.
Oh my god, that was satisfying.
That's what I like to see.
Look at the hammers.
They just died in the boulder.
Very interesting.
Come on.
The nugget is stuck in the boulder.
Nah, that's fine.
I don't need it.
In fact, I have 500 already.
How the hell is that even possible?
Not bad.
I do like the spark bolt with trigger.
Maybe replace this one.
Sure.
Whoops.
Oh, this is already looking bad.
Got him.
Dude, this is a sick wand right now.
It's doing great.
Very good.
Check that one already.
Is that an egg?
No, that's a bone.
Whoa.
Shit.
Oh yeah, you like that?
Oh no.
Be smart.
I'm down here.
Hey.
There we go.
Solid.
Bro, it's so much super good damage with this thing right now.
Like, at this level, in the game, I am doing a good amount of damage.
In fact, I'm not afraid of anything right now.
Ah, this place is... dammit.
Nothing makes...
Forever.
Like that place in there?
I wonder how many other similar places there are in the game that I just don't know about, you know?
That could be...
life-changing.
Ah, sir.
There we go.
Why does it shoot that...
Okay, it's because of the small castellate.
It shoots five spitter bolts in quick succession.
That's the source of that insane DPS.
I can't get through anywhere here.
Or can I?
Wait a minute.
Shit!
Ah well.
I tried.
Not happening.
But that's fine.
I have alternate paths.
And... look, a natto?
I'm tempted to just take this portal.
But I'm not gonna.
I want to do everything in my power to find everything there is to find here.
It's actually so important.
I've seen this exact thing.
Like, this wooden beam with...
Okay, so these levels are made up of...
like handmade tiles, I would say.
And they're just shuffled around.
You know, because I've seen some of these things exactly, unless I'm fucking imagining things.
Like, I've seen that so many times.
Okay, you down there, you need to be watered.
Ah, that's not gonna hit you, is it?
Ow!
This fucker right here.
Nice!
Oops, you have to touch it.
Okay, we can keep going a bit more.
So I gotta keep... look at my phone here.
Where is it there?
Okay.
I keep checking my wants.
Like, oh, do I have a bomb or something?
Even though I don't.
It's like checking the fridge every ten minutes and thinking, oh, is there anything nice to eat in here?
And there's not, you know?
It's the exact same feeling.
That guy's dead.
I don't want to risk it with a biscuit.
Ah, go up here, I guess.
Hemis!
Wow, money.
That was a lot!
That's how we do it.
Dammit, no heart here.
Sometimes there's a heart underneath these.
Okay, 32.
We're getting to that point.
Ah, get some water.
Bro,
I'm earning tons of money.
Like, look at all this.
Too many hemises.
And another wand.
This is solid so far.
Yikes.
That's really bad.
No, thank you.
Wait, what's this?
I can't dig.
That's the shitty wand.
And that's the end of the line.
Okay, I think we have thoroughly explored the hemisphere.
And a thousand gold to our name.
That is not bad.
That's actually really good.
There's no way I'm gonna get in here?
I can maybe get in there.
On the left side.
Here we go.
Ah, this is the spot.
Wait, wait, look, this is the...
You see this?
This is exactly what I'm talking about.
I've seen this exact thing in another place in this level.
Boom.
Oh, he died.
What's that?
Flamox?
You know what?
Let's take it.
I am curious about the flamoxium.
Hey, you know what?
I'm not curious about the flamoxium.
We can actually stay here.
Thank you.
I want that instead.
What was that?
Text in the...
Oh, okay, I see.
Cannot pick flamoxium up because I don't have any space.
Okay, now we can go this way.
And there's nothing here.
So that's my cue.
Let's-a go.
Give me something nice.
Ten mana charge.
Ooh, always cast smo- Ooh, oh!
But a very low mana charge.
It's a bit unfortunate, but I will maybe buy it anyway.
Okay.
What do we got?
Stainless armor.
More blood.
This is the verta, verta, verta.
Creatures become more aggressive towards each other.
Mmm.
I think this one is a good bet.
I'm taking it.
It's a solid thing to buy.
I want this.
Give me that instead of, let's say...
Actually, hold on.
Put this up here.
Buy this one.
Bunch of rocks.
I guess that's nice if I need it later.
What should I put on here?
That's not gonna be very fast.
But it does decent damage, right?
What else can I buy?
I'm not intrigued by a lot of this.
Wait a minute.
No, that's bad.
That's...
actually decent.
That's an okay wand right there.
I may just get it.
Actually, no, this one is better that I have there.
No?
What if I do this?
Ah, still the recharge time being the limiting factor here.
This is actually still a solid wand.
Which one is it that this one always casts the plus damage?
Let's see the recharge on it.
I mean, it's not gonna matter because this one consumes mana so slowly anyway.
But if I do this...
That's not bad.
That's pretty decent.
Now...
Maybe I simply do this.
Ah, so it doesn't go very far though.
That's the issue with that one.
Yeah.
I can also use this.
The fact that it bounces everywhere could come in handy, you know?
It doesn't damage me.
And it's gonna do a decent amount of damage here.
In fact, it does a lot of damage.
I mean, the same amount of damage as the spark bolt, right?
But it is a lot slower.
No, I like this.
I like this.
This is solid.
Put these up here.
Actually, no, put them down here because I don't really want them.
What else should I buy?
I think that's it for now.
Wait, what are these ones?
Oh, these are the little squares that you shoot, right?
Yeah, that seems fine.
Okay, let's go.
Okay, I'm back.
Let's rock and roll.
Slimy egg down there.
Whoa!
Wait.
Oh, right.
There we go.
13 damage.
That's pretty good.
It's actually the exact same amount of damage I had on the spark bolt and luminous trigger.
Or luminous drill thing.
Whoa!
That was sick.
I hit the potion in the air and it exploded and all the stuff fell on him.
Oh, but there's pheromone here.
Would kind of love to get some of that.
What is this?
Purifying powder.
I need an empty potion.
Solid wand here.
Whoa!
Okay, let me go right.
Also, I should really arrange these.
I'm not going to use my third or fourth wand right now at all.
Because they're shit.
I guess I go up here.
Dead end.
And I really need something to dig with.
Whoa!
Did I just quit 160?
There's no way.
Okay.
That's a dead end.
Oh, hold on a second.
We're back.
I forgot to unmute.
Okay, so I'm going to take a quick break.
Quickly get some food in boards and then I'm going to keep playing.
I want to...